{
    "subject": "resource/Prabhakar_Panshikar",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "\u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Prabhakar Panshikar is \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9430567026138306,
            "question": "How would you say Prabhakar Panshikar's name in Hindi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8983298540115356,
            "question": "Is 'Prabhakar Panshikar' a common name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.892641007900238,
            "question": "What is the full name of Prabhakar Panshikar in Marathi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8730222582817078,
            "question": "What are some possible meanings of the names 'Prabhakar' and 'Panshikar'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8561496138572693,
            "question": "What is Prabhakar Panshikar's name spelled phonetically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8059303760528564,
            "question": "How would you write Prabhakar Panshikar's name in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7272883057594299,
            "question": "Is there a difference between Prabhakar Panshikar's name in English and Marathi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6626148223876953,
            "question": "Are there any cultural significance associated with the names \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.581773579120636,
            "question": "What language is \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930 written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4412848651409149,
            "question": "Can you provide the transliteration of \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930 into English?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Prabhakar Panshikar is \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8362_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language is \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930 written in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8362_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any cultural significance associated with the names \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8362_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a difference between Prabhakar Panshikar's name in English and Marathi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8362_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8362_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8362_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8362_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8362_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8362_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8362_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8362_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8362_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8362_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8362_52.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain the information that \"Prabhakar Panshikar (Marathi: \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930)\" which supports the triple that \"The full name of Prabhakar Panshikar is \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Prabhakar Panshikar, including his full name as \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930 in Devanagari script. Therefore, the statement that his full name is \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0915\u0930 \u092a\u0923\u0936\u0940\u0915\u0930 is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}